Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Chicks on Speed, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Collins, Billy (shelved in oversize box), undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Cronenberg, David, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cusimano, Mick, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Daitch, Susan, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Dalachinsky, Steven, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Dombrowski, Bob, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Doucet, Julie, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Feast, Jim, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - FLY, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Gray, Spaulding, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Hughes Brothers, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Hunter, Keshav, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Kaz, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Krigstein, Bernard, undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Lane, Tim, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Long, Donald, undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Maurer, Susan (shelved in oversize box), undated (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Mesmer, Susan, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - No-Neck Blues Band, undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Otomo, Yuko, undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Pincus, Henry, undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Pyle, Kevin, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Rutkowski, Thad, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Rutkowski, Thad (as Hip Hop Sing), undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Seth, undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Seth (shelved in oversize box), undated (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Sonnenfeld, Mark, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Sparrow, undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Sparrow (shelved in oversize box), undated (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Spiegelman, Arthur, undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Ulin, David, undated (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Welch, Sean Michael, undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Witz, Bob, undated (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Zummer, Tom, undated (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects
    - Bitaemo (Ukranian Restaurant), undated (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Coliseum Books, Ron Kolm collage, undated (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Coliseum Books, Boycott Flyer, undated (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Coliseum Books, Patron Business Cards, undated (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Coliseum Books, store closing, memos, undated (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Coliseum Books, store closing, Ron Kolm interview, undated (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Coliseum Books, store closing, clippings, undated (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Coliseum Books, correspondence, Anthony Ballard, undated (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Coliseum Books, correspondence, Ron Kolm, undated (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Coliseum Books, correspondence, John Underwood, undated (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Coliseum Books, misc. correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Coliseum Books, employee art, Meg's Hats, undated (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Coliseum Books, employee art, cards by Patrick Stevenson, undated (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Coliseum Books, misc. employee art, undated (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Coliseum Books, ephemera, undated (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Coliseum Books, flyers, undated (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Coliseum Books, invitations, undated (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Coliseum Books, ID cards, Ron Kolm, undated (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Coliseum Books, Only in New York, undated (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Coliseum Books, policies, information, undated (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Coliseum Books, press clippings, undated (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - Coliseum Books, re-opening, undated (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Coliseum Books, sound recording, employee mix CD-RS, undated (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Coliseum Books, sound recording, None of the Above "Feel Like a Dog" 45 inch single, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Coliseum Books, staff events, undated (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Coliseum Books, in-store readings, undated (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Klezmer, undated (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Pacifica Radio, undated (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Semiotext(e), undated (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - September 11th 2001, undated (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - Shakespeare and Company, undated (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Soft Skull Press, undated (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series V: Photographs
  - Subseries A: Photographs
    - 2 photos of Ron Kolm at the Nuyorican, undated (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - 2 photos of Ron Kolm reading at Bergen Community College, undated (Box 27, Folder 80)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries A: Readings
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Anthology Film Archives, undated (Box 27, Folder 82)
    - Art Resources Transfer, undated (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - Artists Space, undated (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - Back Fence, undated (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - Barnes & Noble, Astor Place, undated (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Bergen Community College, undated (Box 27, Folder 87)
    - Bowery Poetry Club, undated (Box 27, Folder 88)
    - Brecht Forum, undated (Box 27, Folder 89)
    - Canadian Consulate, undated (Box 27, Folder 90)
    - CBGB's Lounge, undated (Box 27, Folder 91)
    - Cedar Tavern, undated (Box 27, Folder 92)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated (Box 27, Folder 93)
    - Clemente Soto Velez Cultural Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 94)
    - Cohan, Leslie and Browne, undated (Box 27, Folder 95)
    - Columbia University, undated (Box 27, Folder 96)
    - Cornelia Street Café, undated (Box 27, Folder 97)
    - Cowell Theater, undated (Box 27, Folder 98)
    - Dabora, undated (Box 27, Folder 99)
    - DIA Center for the Arts, undated (Box 27, Folder 100)
    - Double Happiness, undated (Box 27, Folder 101)
    - Downtown Music Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 102)
    - The Educational Alliance, undated (Box 27, Folder 103)
    - Fales Library, NYU, undated (Box 27, Folder 104)
    - FUN, undated (Box 27, Folder 105)
    - Gallery One Twenty Eight, undated (Box 27, Folder 106)
    - Holland Tunnel, undated (Box 27, Folder 107)
    - Housing Works Bookstore and Café, undated (Box 27, Folder 108)
    - http://members.theglobe.com/verlaine37, undated (Box 27, Folder 109)
    - Knitting Factory, undated (Box 27, Folder 110)
    - Life Café, undated (Box 27, Folder 111)
    - Little Theater, undated (Box 27, Folder 112)
    - M Shanghai, undated (Box 27, Folder 113)
    - Manhattan Table Tennis Club, undated (Box 27, Folder 114)
    - Mission Café, undated (Box 27, Folder 115)
    - Moroccan Star, undated (Box 27, Folder 116)
    - New York Open Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 117)
    - New York University, undated (Box 27, Folder 118)
    - P.S. 3, undated (Box 27, Folder 119)
    - Pantheon Theater, undated (Box 27, Folder 120)
    - Poet to Poet, undated (Box 27, Folder 121)
    - The Poetry Event Schedule, undated (Box 27, Folder 122)
    - Poets House, undated (Box 27, Folder 123)
    - Polestar Music Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 124)
    - Printed Matter, Inc., undated (Box 27, Folder 125)
    - The Read, undated (Box 27, Folder 126)
    - Saint Lawrence University, undated (Box 27, Folder 127)
    - Saint Mark's Church, undated (Box 27, Folder 128)
    - Serendipity 3, undated (Box 27, Folder 129)
    - Sideshow, undated (Box 27, Folder 130)
    - 6th Street Garden, undated (Box 27, Folder 131)
    - Small Press Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 132)
    - Starett Lehigh Building, undated (Box 27, Folder 133)
    - Teachers and Writers Collaborative, undated (Box 27, Folder 134)
    - Tibet House, undated (Box 27, Folder 135)
    - Tonic, undated (Box 27, Folder 136)
    - TRIAD, undated (Box 27, Folder 137)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 138)
    - Woodstock Poetry Festival, undated (Box 27, Folder 139)
    - Wythe Studio, undated (Box 27, Folder 140)
    - Zinc Bar, undated (Box 27, Folder 141)
    - Unspecified / Multiple Venue, undated (Box 27, Folder 142)
    - Unspecified (shelved in oversize box), undated (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 27, Folder 143)
    - Anthology Film Archive, undated (Box 27, Folder 144)
    - Ben Shahn Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 145)
    - Bindlestiff Family Cirkus, undated (Box 27, Folder 146)
    - B'Nai Jeshurun, undated (Box 27, Folder 147)
    - Brooke Alexander, undated (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - Candle Lite Restaurant, undated (Box 27, Folder 149)
    - Central Park, undated (Box 27, Folder 150)
    - Charles Cowles Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 151)
    - Clayton Patterson Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 152)
    - C.U.A.N.D.O., undated (Box 27, Folder 153)
    - David Allen, undated (Box 27, Folder 154)
    - Derapage Controle II, undated (Box 27, Folder 155)
    - DIA Center for the Arts, undated (Box 27, Folder 156)
    - Dolan / Maxwell, undated (Box 27, Folder 157)
    - Dorfman Projects, undated (Box 27, Folder 158)
    - Duplex Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 159)
    - Elizabeth Harris Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 160)
    - Elsa Dorfman, undated (Box 27, Folder 161)
    - Fire Monkey, undated (Box 27, Folder 162)
    - The Flea, undated (Box 27, Folder 163)
    - Florence Lynch Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 164)
    - Fordham University Theatre Co., undated (Box 27, Folder 165)
    - Fredericke Taylor Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 166)
    - Frying Pan, undated (Box 27, Folder 167)
    - Gallery X, undated (Box 27, Folder 168)
    - Gershwin Hotel, undated (Box 27, Folder 169)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 170)
    - Grey Art Gallery, undated (Box 27, Folder 171)
    - Hebrew Home at Riverdale, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - James Gat Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - K2 Dance and Arts Company, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Lark Theatre Company, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Lindsey Brown, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Lunatarium, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - La Maison Francaise of NYU, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Marcel Sitcoske Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - MIT Media Lab, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Medicine Show, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitan Pavilion, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Mitchell Algus Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - North Six, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - P.P.O.W., undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - P.S. 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Participant, Inc., undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - La Perla Garden, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Le Petit Versailles, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Phyllis Kind Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - S. Conzo Pizzeria, undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Shelley Himmelstein, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Sideshow, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Sin Festival 2001, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Small, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Spa, undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Studio 18 Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Taipei Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Theater for the New City, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - 30th Street Theater, undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Times Square Lobby Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Two Boots, undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - 2/20 Gallery, undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - University Libraries: SUNY Buffalo, undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - University of the Arts, undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Upstate Art, undated (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Warsaw, undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - www.skhsculpture.com, undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Yoga People, undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Multiple / Unspecified Venues, undated (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VII: Sound recordings
  - Algebra Suicide. The Secret Like Crazy. Compact Disk., 1987 (Box 30)
  - Algebra Suicide. Tongue Wrestling. Compact Disk., 1994 (Box 30)
  - Dalachinsky, Steve. I thought it was the end of the world then…. Compact Disc., 2002 (Box 30)
  - Lingo CD #1. Compact Disc., undated (Box 30)
  - Miles, Nick. Face Down in the Gutter of Love. Compact Disk., undated (Box 30)
  - Tomkiw, Lydia. Incorporated. Compact Disk., 1995 (Box 30)
  - Staggered Thirds. Live. 80 min Recordable Compact Disk., 11/2001 (Box 30)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VIII: Original Art
  - Appearances Magazine: Pieces by Patty Kirschner and Himmelstein, undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Aronson, David-"Obsession" drawing, JPEG on 3¼ inch Mac and IBM floppy discs, undated (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Brown, Ken-11 pieces, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Madore, Michael-10 pieces, undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Moore, Thurston-Untitled, undated (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Zummer, Tom-"Plan for the Invasion of California", undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - 3 unsigned, untitled pieces, undated (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series IX: Ephemera
  - Next Tribe Sticker, undated (Box 28, Folder 48)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XI: Posters
  - Barnes & Noble Writers on the Edge Series Featuring Susan Sherman and Ron Kolm, undated (Folder 10 Right)
  - Huerta, Antonio Estevan, undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 5)
  - Lab U.S.A. Illuminated Documents, undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 6)
  - Lower East Side Festival of the Arts, undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 3)
  - St. Mark's Poetry Project New Year 2002 Marathon Reading (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 1)
  - St. Mark's Poetry Project New Year 2003 Marathon Reading (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 2)
  - World Week, undated (Folder 4 Left)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XII: Catalogs
  - Alice James Books, Spring 2002 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Autonomedia, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Autonomedia Calendar of Jubilee Saints (Shelved in oversize box), 2003 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_8f9b16fa4a149b82a99948c3280773b6)
  - City Lights, Spring/Summer 2002, Fall/Winter 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Dalkey Archive, Spring 2003 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Drawn & Quarterly, Spring 2003 catalogue and sampler (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Four Walls Eight Windows, Fall 2001, Spring 2002, Fall 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Hanging Loose Press, 2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - J. N. Herlin, nos. 2, 3, 6, 7, undated (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - J. N. Herlin, 1982 Special Lists 17-20, Catalogue # 8, Special List 23, undated (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Mother Jones Fine Print Portfolio, undated (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Poet's House Exhibit Catalogue, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Seven Stories Press, Fall 2001, Fall/Winter 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Small Press Distribution, Spring/Summer 2002, Fall/Winter 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Soft Skull Press, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - South End Press, Spring 2002 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Verso, Spring 2002, Autumn 2002, Spring 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 64)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XIV: Periodicals
  Selected Periodicals were removed to the Downtown Periodical Collection and individually catalogued. These materials are also listed in the Separated Materials portion of this finding aid.
  - A&U 11.9 (September 2002) (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Anthology Film Archives (April-June 2002)-(April-June 2003), 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Bookforum (Fall 2002); (Winter 2002); (Spring 2003) (shelved in oversize box), 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Ecstatic Peace 5 (Winter-Spring 2003) (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Emo 8 (December 2001) (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Gay City News 1.16 (September 13-19, 2002) (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - Misc. 114 (Autumn 2001); 116 (Spring 2002), 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Monkey Puzzle 1 (Fall 2002) (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - New York Nights 1, 4, 9, 11, undated (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - The New Yorker (9/3/2001), (9/24/2001) (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - Punk Planet Magazine 49 (May-June 2002) (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - 6 x 6 #4 (September 2001) "Hog-tied in the Parking Lot Like Firemen" (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - Small Press Review (January-February 2002)-(March-April 2003), 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Smithsonian 33.8 (November 2002) (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - Ur Vox 1 (2001) (Box 28, Folder 78)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Oversize - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Collins, Billy (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Maurer, Susan (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Seth (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Sparrow (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Oversize - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries A: Readings
    - Unspecified Venue (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Oversize - Series XII: Catalogs
  - Autonomedia Calendar of Jubilee Saints (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Oversize - Series XIV
  - Book Forum (Fall 2002, Winter 2002, Spring 2003) (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Accretions 2000-2003 - Oversize - Series XI: Posters
  - Plaza de la Revolucion, Havana, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Accretions 2000-2003 - Oversize - Series XIII: Calendars
  - 2001 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 2002 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Accretions 2000-2003 - Oversize - Series XIV: Periodicals
  - American Book Review (Jan-Feb 2002, Mar-Apr 2002) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - American Book Review (Sept-Oct 2002, Nov-Dec 2002) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Beatlick News (Dec 2001, March 2002) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Boog City (issues 2,3,4,5,6) (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - The Brooklyn Rail (Jan-Feb 2002, Mar-Apr 2002) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Context (issues 8,9) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Homeplanet News (issue 48) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - MISC (winter 2002 issue) (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - New York Nights (issues 1,4,5,7) (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - New York Waste (Feb 2002) (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Small Press Review (Nov-Dec 2002) (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Accretions 2015-2016
  These accretions have not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  These accretions consist of materials collected by Ron Kolm documenting the Soho and East Village arts and literary scenes, primarily in the years 2014-2016. Materials include flyers for poetry readings and other literary events; gallery announcements; promotional materials for upcoming books; correspondence with artists and writers; manuscripts in various stages; audio recordings; video recordings; and publications, including zines, newspapers, magazines, and literary journals.
  Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - American Academy of Letters, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Steve Dalachnsky, Eight Pound Dog, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Music and Literary Ephemera, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Publications, 2001-2016 (Box 38, Folder 4-12, Folder 18-20, Box 39, Folder 13-16)
  - New York Newspapers, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 13, Box 39, Folder 11-12, Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2015-2016 (Box 38, Folder 14-15, Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Local Knowledge, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Poet's House Exhibition Catalog, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Brevitas, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Kathy Acker Photograph, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - 100 Thousand Poets for Change, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Ephemera, 2014-2016 (Box 38, Folder 24-27, Box 39, Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Poetry and Other Writings, 2014-2016 (Box 39, Folder 2-10)
  - Jeffrey Cyphers Wright Poetry, 1985-1987 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Murder at the CIA Lounge by Theodore Weaver, 2015 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Poet's House Showcase Exhibition Catalog and Reading Flyers, 2016
  - Boog City #10 Materials, 2016 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Patti Smith Reading, 2016-04-19 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Night Shift by Ron Kolm, 2016 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Su Polo Saturn Series Readings, 2016 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - John Farris Memorial, 2016-04-29 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Matty Jankowski Piece for Clayton's Tattoo Book, 2016 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - "Damaged Goods" by Ron Kolm, 2016 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Alternative New Year's Day Reading Materials, 2015-2016 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Jim Feast Review of Ron Kolm's Duke and Jill, 2016 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Autonomedia Calendar, 2016 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Audio Recordings, 2015-2016 (Box 40)
  - Video Recordings, 2015-2016 (Box 40)
- Accretions 2018, 1978-2017; 2015-2017; 2 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize file folder; 4 dvd-r disks; 4 sound discs (cd)
  This accretion contains materials collected by Ron Kolm, documenting the Soho and East Village arts and literary scene. Materials include ephemera for events, gallery announcements, correspondence, newspapers, and literary and cultural publications. This accretion also includes audio and video recordings of literary and poetry readings, John Farris Memorial Service, and commercial music albums.
  - Literary Event Ephemera, Manuscripts, and Correspondence, 1978-2017 (Box 56, Folder 1-19, Box 59)
  - Newspaper, Calendar, Event and Bookstore Posters, 2016 (Box 37, Folder 10, Box 60)
- Accretions 2019, 1975-2018; 4.75 linear feet in 3 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 oversize folder in shared housing, and 1 flat-file
  This accretion contains materials collected by Ron Kolm, documenting the Soho and East Village arts and literary scene. Materials include ephemera for events, gallery announcements, clippings, and newspapers. Also included in this accretion are small distribution publishing company catalogs and manuscripts for various writers.
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - Correspondence, 2016-2018 (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
  - Ellen Aug Lytle -- Alternative New Year's Day Reading Series, 1995-2015 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Ellen Aug Lytle -- Flyers for Workshops and Readings, 1975-2013 (Box 61, Folder 6-9)
  - Ellen Aug Lytle -- Clippings, 1976-1991 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - From Somewhere to Nowhere: The End of the American Dream (First Print), 2017 (Box 61, Folder 11-13, Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Jeffrey Cyphers Wright, 2017-2018 (Box 62, Folder 2-8)
  - Sparrow, 2013-2014 (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
  - Waterkeeper Alliance, 2017 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Richard West, 1975-2018 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Brevitas Reading, 2017 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Shalom Neuman and Unbs Antu, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Holly Anderson Memorial, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Thad Rutkowski, 1989-2007 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 100,000 Poets for Change, 2017 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Cafe Review, 2017 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Amy Wilson, Michael Lindgren, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - "A Late Lunch with Philip Roth", 2019 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Amy Barone, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Unbearables and Ron Kolm, 2017-2018 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Exodusa (Joe Carey), 2017 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Neo Phobe, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Tribes #15, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Prague, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - John Farris, 2016 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Poems by Tom Savage, Steve Dalachinsky, Francine Witte, and Others, 1999-2017 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - "The Ultimate Business of Murder," Spryg, 2016 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - David Huberman, 2018 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Steve Dalachinsky, 2000-2018 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Ephemera, circa 2016-2019 (Box 64, Box Shared Fales Accessions 001, Folder 5)
  - Publications, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 65, Box 66)
  - Calendars, Posters, 2017-2018 (Box Shared Fales 028, Folder 12, Folder 21)